Simon Fraser University Women's Centre fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Organization records, 1974 - 1998; F-40-4; 37 cm of textual records
  - Women's Centre planning files, 1991 - 1998; F-40-4-6; 5 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the long-term and short-term planning programs of the Women's Centre. Activities and topics documented include proposed activities and programming, Centre priorities, mission statement and mandate of the Centre, roles and responsibilities of collective members and staff, infrastructure of the Centre, staff evaluation procedures, promotion and publicity strategy, and liaison with other campus groups. Records include agendas, minutes, proposals, notes, drafts, reports, and flyers.
    - Fall planning session, 1991; F-40-4-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 40-17)
    - Long-range planning workshop, 1991; F-40-4-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 40-17)
    - Planning workshop, 1991 - 1992; F-40-4-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 40-17)
    - Minutes: promotion/publicity meetings, 1992; F-40-4-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 40-17)
    - Reflection meeting, 1998; F-40-4-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 40-17)
  - Women's Centre Collective membership files, 1994; F-40-4-7; 1 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the 1994 membership collective of the Women's Centre. File consists of a set of 4 x 6 inch cards. Each card contains a photograph of the woman and her personal statement regarding her background and experience, her vision for the Women's Centre, what she hoped to contribute to the Centre, and what she hoped to gain from her participation in the Collective.
    - Fall '94 Collective, 1994; F-40-4-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 40-17)
  - Women's Centre Herstory, 1980 - 1991; F-40-4-8; 1 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the history of the SFSS Women's Centre. Records include drafts, notes, newsletters, and printed articles.
    - Women's Centre Herstory, [1980?] - 1991; F-40-4-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 40-17)
- Education, advocacy and outreach files, 1970 - 2000; F-40-5; 1.12 m of textual records 89 photographs 4 slides 2 artifacts; General note: photographs are found in sub-series 7; the artifacts (a button and a pin from the December 6 vigil in 1993) are found in sub-series 2, Celebrations and special events, file F-40-5-2-0-3, December 6 Vigil, 1993.
  Series comprises records relating to the planning, organization and implementation of Women's Centre projects, programs and events. Activities documented include International Women's Day events, December 6 vigils, and film nights; interventions on campus issues and controversies such as pornography on campus and the development of the Harassment Policy; workshops; participation in conferences; and a survey of Women's Centre users (1981). Records include correspondence; proposals and reports; programs and presentations; notes, drafts and working papers; brochures, posters and other publicity material; press clippings; meeting minutes; survey data and analysis; and photographs.
  In the original arrangement of the fonds (2001), this series was titled "Projects, programs and events files" and contained no sub-series. In the 2009 processing of new accruals, the archivist re-organized the files into a number of sub-series due to the large volume of material. Files included under the 2001 arrangement had their reference codes re-assigned; see Appendix D for a concordance between the previous and current file code numbers.
  - General files, 1976 - 1999; F-40-5-1; 7 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records relating to general programming initiatives of the Women's Centre and general information on topics of interest. Records include correspondence, surveys, flyers, pamphlets, news clippings, notes and other documents.
    - Programs - general, 1976 - 1981; F-40-5-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 40-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-20.
    - Women's Centre survey, 1981; F-40-5-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 40-8)
      Restricted in part
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-25.
    - Sexual harassment, 1981 - 1984; F-40-5-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-13.
    - Childhood sexual abuse programming, 1991 - 1993; F-40-5-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-3.
    - General programming ideas, 1991 - 1996; F-40-5-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 40-17)
    - Collage Project, 1998; F-40-5-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 40-18)
    - Community Resource Project, 1999; F-40-5-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 40-18)
  - Celebrations and special events files, 1986 - 1999; F-40-5-2; 35 cm of textual records 2 artifacts; General note: the artifacts (a button and a pin from the December 6 vigil in 1993) are found in file F-40-5-2-0-3, December 6 Vigil, 1993.
    Subseries consists of records relating to particular commemorative or celebratory events concerned with feminist issues. Records include flyers, correspondence, notes, minutes, programs and news clippings.
    - December 6 Vigil, 1991; F-40-5-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-5.
    - December 6 Vigil, 1992; F-40-5-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-6.
    - December 6 Vigil, 1993; F-40-5-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-7.
    - International Women's Day Film Festival, 1986; F-40-5-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-8.
    - International Women's Day, 1986 - 1991; F-40-5-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-9.
    - International Women's Day, 1992; F-40-5-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-10.
    - December 6 Vigil, 1991 - 1994; F-40-5-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 40-18)
    - Services Day, 1992; F-40-5-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 40-18)
    - 25th anniversary (Oct. 1993), F-40-5-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 40-18)
    - International Women's Day, 1993; F-40-5-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 40-18)
    - Black History Month, 1993 - 1997; F-40-5-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 40-18)
    - International Women's Day, 1994; F-40-5-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 40-18)
    - December 6 Vigil, 1994 - 1995; F-40-5-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 40-18)
    - International Women's Day, 1994 - 1995; F-40-5-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 40-18)
    - Eating Disorder Awareness Week, 1994 - 1996; F-40-5-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - India Night (Mar. 1995), F-40-5-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - International Lesbian Week (Feb. 1995), F-40-5-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - December 6 Vigil, 1995 - 1996; F-40-5-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - International Women's Day, 1995 - 1996; F-40-5-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - December 6 Vigil, 1995 - 1997; F-40-5-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - Global Carnival (Mar. 1996), F-40-5-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - December 6 Vigil, 1996 - 1997; F-40-5-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - Eating Disorder Awareness Week (Feb. 1997), 1996 - 1997; F-40-5-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - Rotunda party with PIRG and OOC (Nov. 1996), 1996 - 1997; F-40-5-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - Fat Happiness Day (Feb. 1997), F-40-5-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - First Nations Festival (Nov. 1997), F-40-5-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - International Women's Day, 1997; F-40-5-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - Take Back the Night (Sept. 1997), F-40-5-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - Eating Disorder Awareness Week, 1997 - 1998; F-40-5-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - Aboriginal Awareness Day (Mar. 1998), F-40-5-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 40-19)
    - December 6 Vigil, 1998; F-40-5-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - International Women's Day, 1998; F-40-5-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Women's Centre Social (Nov. 1998), F-40-5-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Eating Disorder Awareness Week, 1998 - 1999; F-40-5-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Black History Month (Feb. 1999), F-40-5-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - December 6 Vigil, 1999; F-40-5-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Fat Happiness Day (Feb. 1999), F-40-5-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - International Women's Day, 1999; F-40-5-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
  - Conferences, presentations and workshop files, 1975 - 2000; F-40-5-3; 28 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to public education events hosted or attended by the Women's Centre. Records include flyers, correspondence, notes, minutes, programs and news clippings.
    - Symposium for Peer Leaders and Student Helpers (SPLASH) conference, 1992; F-40-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 40-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-22.
    - Women's Centre conference, 1975; F-40-5-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 40-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-23.
    - Racism workshop (Aug. 13, 1990), F-40-5-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
      Open, reading room
      Reviewed for access (Dec 5, 2023) – File includes records that contain some individuals' personal contact information. File can be accessed in the Archives' reading room, but will be redacted in any digital access copies made by Archives.
    - Presentation to SFU Nightline volunteers, 1991 - 1994; F-40-5-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Women's Spirituality (Jan. 19 and 26, 1992), 1991 - 1992; F-40-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - National Clearinghouse on Marital and Date Rape -- proposed speaker, 1992; F-40-5-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Summer Institute for Union Women, 1992 - 1997; F-40-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Disabled and Proud: the 1993 National Gathering of College Student Leaders with Disabilities conference, F-40-5-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Unlearning Racism workshops, Celeste George (Nov. 5 and 19, 1993), F-40-5-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Safe Sex (Nov. 16, 1994), F-40-5-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Self-Defence and Assertiveness for Women -- proposal by Laurie Schuerbeke, 1994; F-40-5-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Zagreb Report (Mar. 28, 1995), 1994 - 1995; F-40-5-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 40-20)
    - Unlearning Racism, Donna Lee and Man Chui Leung (Apr. 2, 1995), F-40-5-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
    - Unlearning Racism, Sadie Kuehn (Apr. 6, May 10 and 28, 1995), F-40-5-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
      Open, no restrictions
      Reviewed for access (Dec 5, 2023) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - Unlearning Racism, Sadie Kuehn (Jan. 20, 1996), 1995 - 1996; F-40-5-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
    - Beijing follow-up (Nov. 15, 1995), F-40-5-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
    - Dealing with Stress: Naturopathic Medicine and Women's Health (Jan. 30, 1996), F-40-5-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
    - Alexander Technique (Oct. 22, 1996), F-40-5-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
    - Pornography: the Personal and Political Dilemma (Sept. 26, 1996) -- administrative/planning, 1996 - 1997; F-40-5-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
    - Pornography: the Personal and Political Dilemma -- administrative/planning, 1996; F-40-5-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
    - Pornography: the Personal and Political Dilemma -- porn - selected readings, Collective reviewed, summer 1996, F-40-5-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
    - Pornography: the Personal and Political Dilemma -- bibliography, 1996; F-40-5-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
    - Pornography: the Personal and Political Dilemma -- "Pornogate" history, 1996; F-40-5-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 40-21)
    - Pornography: the Personal and Political Dilemma -- SFU Women's Centre response: Peak letter, brief, fact sheet, 1996; F-40-5-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Facilitation workshop (Sept. 30, 1997), F-40-5-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - First Nations Women's Speakers Series (June 19 and 26, July 3 and 10, 1997), 1997 - 1998; F-40-5-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Women and APEC workshop (Oct. 8 1997), F-40-5-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Human rights workshop (Jan. 15, 1998), 1997 - 1998; F-40-5-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Spirituality diversity panel, SFPIRG (Mar. 10, 1998), F-40-5-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Natural Remedies workshop (July 24, 1998), F-40-5-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Aboriginal Herb Walk and Workshop (Sept. 29, 1998), F-40-5-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - ANAD - disordered eating conference (Mar. 26-29, 1999), F-40-5-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Canadian Student Conference on Campus Sexual Violence (Nov. 5-7, 1999), 1999 - 2000; F-40-5-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Sacred sexuality workshop (Nov. 10, 1999), F-40-5-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
  - Support and discussion group files, 1992 - 1997; F-40-5-4; 2 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the activities of support and discussion groups related to feminist issues. Records include flyers, correspondence, notes, minutes, programs and news clippings.
    - ROC: 'Riot of Colour', 1992 - 1993; F-40-5-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Women and Bisexuality, 1995 - 1996; F-40-5-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Women's Writing Group, 1996 - 1997; F-40-5-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Anti-Oppression group, 1996 - 1997; F-40-5-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
  - On-campus issues files, 1981 - 1996; F-40-5-5; 8 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the Women's Centre's involvement in campus issues, including childcare, student activism, pornography on campus computer systems, sexual harassment, and labour conflicts. Records include correspondence, notes, minutes, drafts, policies, news clippings, posters, and flyers.
    - Issues - pornography on Campus, 1982; F-40-5-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-11.
    - Issues - Northern Assault poster, vol. 1, 1992; F-40-5-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-12.
    - Daycare, 1981 - 1983; F-40-5-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Campus Grad Sudent Childcare Committee, 1991; F-40-5-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Activists' Network, 1992; F-40-5-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Playboy subscription - SFU library, 1992; F-40-5-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Pornography on NetNews, 1992 - 1993; F-40-5-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 40-22)
    - Response to 'Women of the Veil' articles in the Vancouver Sun, 1992; F-40-5-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Racism - letter to Pulp Press, 1992; F-40-5-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Sexual harassment charges within SFSS executive, 1992 - 1994; F-40-5-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Empire Maintenance Services (campus cleaning contract), 1994; F-40-5-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Harassment by pub employee, 1995; F-40-5-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - GlobeVote, 1996; F-40-5-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Oversize posters, [ca 1989] - [ca 1992]; F-40-5-5-0-14
      Graphic materials
    - Issues - Northern Assault poster, vol. 2, 1992; F-40-5-5-0-15
  - Off-campus issues files, 1975 - 2000; F-40-5-6; 22 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the Centre's involvement in feminist issues of a more general nature extending beyond the SFU campus, including the portrayal of women in the media, abortion, homophobia, violence against women, gun control, immigration, sexual harassment, children's rights, and other topics. For a list of organizations included in the correspondence, see "Access points" below. Records include correspondence, notes, minutes, drafts, policies, news clippings, flyers, newsletters, and reports.
    Community Teledon Network of the Pacific; Canadian Abortion Rights Action League; Media Watch; Canadian Research Institute for the Advancement of Women; Women's International League for Peace and Freedom; University of British Columbia (UBC); University of Toronto. Committee on Homophobia; Canadian Panel on Violence Against Women; Coalition for Gun Control; Law Society of British Columbia; Vancouver Society on Immigrant Women; Langara College; Canadian Federation of University Women; Canadian Congress for Learning Opportunities for Women; Women's Monument Project; Canadian Association Against Sexual Harassment in Higher Education; Lower Mainland Women's Lobbying Coalition; Society for Children's Right to Adequate Parental Support; Disabled Women's Network of British Columbia; Sanctuary Foundation; University of Victoria. Political Science Department
    - Community Telidon Network of the Pacific, 1982 - 1983; F-40-5-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-4.
    - CARAL - Canadian Abortion Rights Action League, 1975 - 1987; F-40-5-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Boycott of film as pornography - De Palma's "Dressed to Kill", [1980?]; F-40-5-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Media Watch, 1983 - 1993; F-40-5-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - CRIAW - Canadian Research Institute for the Advancement of Women, 1989 - 1992; F-40-5-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - WILPF - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1989 - 1992; F-40-5-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - University of BC, 1989 - 1995; F-40-5-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Gay Games, 1990; F-40-5-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Committee on Homophobia - University of Toronto, 1990 - 1991; F-40-5-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Canadian Panel on Violence Against Women, 1991; F-40-5-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Coalition for Gun Control, 1991; F-40-5-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Law Society of BC - Gender Bias Committee, 1991; F-40-5-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Fundraising for 'Christmas Project', 1991 - 1992; F-40-5-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Midwifery Task Force, 1991 - 1992; F-40-5-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Vancouver Society on Immigrant Women, 1991 - 1992; F-40-5-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Langara - sexual harassment, 1991 - 1994; F-40-5-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - CFUW - Canadian Federation of University Women, 1991 - 1995; F-40-5-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - CCLOW - Canadian Congress for Learning Opportunities for Women, 1991 - 1996; F-40-5-6-0-18 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Women's Monument Project (Capilano College), 1991 - 1999; F-40-5-6-0-19 (Archival box - standard 40-23)
    - Canadian Association Against Sexual Harassment in Higher Education, 1990 - 1992; F-40-5-6-0-20 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
    - Grupo Venancia, 1992; F-40-5-6-0-21 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
    - Lower Mainland Women's Lobbying Coalition (1991-1992), F-40-5-6-0-22 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
    - SCRAPS - Society for Children's Right to Adequate Parental Support, 1992; F-40-5-6-0-23 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
    - Women's Groups' Networking Meetings, 1992; F-40-5-6-0-24 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
    - DAWN - Disabled Women's Network, 1992 - 1993; F-40-5-6-0-25 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
    - Sanctuary Foundation, 1992 - 1993; F-40-5-6-0-26 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
    - Women in View Festival, 1992 - 1995; F-40-5-6-0-27 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
    - University of Victoria - Political Science Department (summer 1993), 1993 - 1994; F-40-5-6-0-28 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
    - WOW - Write Out West conference, 1997 - 1998; F-40-5-6-0-29 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
    - DVERS - Domestic Violence Emergency Response System, Burnaby, 1999 - 2000; F-40-5-6-0-30 (Archival box - standard 40-24)
  - Photographs, [197-?] - 1991; F-40-5-7; 89 photographs 4 slides
    Sub-series consists of informal photographs and slide transparencies of Women's Centre social events, parties, retreats, meetings, collective members, and the interior of the Women's Centre.
    - Photographs, [ca 1981]; F-40-5-7-0-1 (Archival box - small 40-28)
      Photographic materials
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-17.
      Reviewed for access (Feb 14, 2024) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - Photographs, [197-?]; F-40-5-7-0-2 (Archival box - small 40-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-18.
    - Photographs and slides, 1990 - 1991; F-40-5-7-0-3 (Archival box - small 40-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-19.
  - Promotion and communication files, 1970 - 1999; F-40-5-8; 10 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the promotion of Women's Centre programs and activities, the production of the Women's Centre newsletter and zine, and production of The Peak column "Surfacing." Records include posters, brochures, artwork, newsletters, and news clippings.
    - Brochures, posters, art, 1976 - 1987; F-40-5-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Subseries consists of promotional material relating to Women's Centre programs and events, production of the Women's Centre newsletter and the Women's Centre zine and Peak articles including the Peak's "Surfacing" column (1974-1975). Records consist of brochures, posters, artwork, newsletters, drafts and working papers,
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-1.
    - Brochures, posters, art, 1981 - 1982; F-40-5-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 40-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-2.
    - Surfacing - The Peak column, 1974 - 1975; F-40-5-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 40-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-21.
    - Women's Centre Newsletter, 1976 - 1982; F-40-5-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 40-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-40-5-0-0-24.
    - Original posters, [ca 1982] - [ca 1983]; F-40-5-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 40-25)
    - Women's Centre Newsletter, 1976 - 1982; F-40-5-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 40-25)
    - Women's Centre zine: "Forbidden Fury: Women Write Life", 1998; F-40-5-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 40-25)
    - Women's Centre zine: "Forbidden Fury: Women Write Life", 1998 - 1999; F-40-5-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 40-25)
- Reference files, 1972 - 1992; F-40-6; 28 cm of textual records 9 sound recordings; Physical description: series includes 9 sound recordings stored on 7 audio cassettes (originals).